Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - Members of Mayday - 10 in 10, 2001; SR-21487; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 7432183943 1; A-side Matrix # B143905-01 A1 HL
        - Members of Mayday - 10 in 10, 2001; SR-21488; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 74321 84563 1; A-side Matrix # B145062-01 A1 MK
        - Members of Mayday - Culture flash, 2002; SR-21489; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 7432192608 1; A-side Matrix # B259139-01 A1 HL
        - Members of Mayday - The day x, 1996; SR-21490; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 576 467-1; A-side Matrix # 576 467-1 A
        - Members of Mayday - The day x (remixes), 1996; SR-21491; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 576 803-1; A-side Matrix # 576 803-1 A
        - Members of Mayday - Live at the sonic empire, 1997; SR-21492; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 74321 501380 1; A-side Matrix # 74321501381-A
        - Members of Mayday - Live at the sonic empire, 1997; SR-21493; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
        - Members of Mayday - Sonic empire, 1997; SR-21494; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21495. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # 74321 47530 1; A-side Matrix # 74321475301-A1
        - Members of Mayday - Sonic empire, 1997; SR-21495; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21494. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Memphis Bleek - Round here, 2003; SR-21496; Memphis Bleek; T.I.; Trick Daddy (Box 355)
          Catalog # DEFR 15967-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15967-1-A
        - Memphis Bleek - Like that, 2005; SR-21497; Memphis Bleek (Box 355)
          Catalog # DEFR 16190-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16190-1-A
        - Memphis Bleek - The one, 2005; SR-21498; Memphis Bleek; Rihanna (Box 355)
          Catalog # DEFR 16348-1; A-side Matrix # B0005030-11-A1
        - Memphis Bleek - Is that your chick, 2000; SR-21499; Memphis Bleek; Jay-Z; Missy Elliot (Box 355)
          Catalog # 314 562 865-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15111-1A
        - Memphis Bleek - 534 (disc one), 2005; SR-21500; Memphis Bleek (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21501. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004164-01; A-side Matrix # B004164-01 LP01-A
        - Memphis Bleek - 534 (disc two), 2005; SR-21501; Memphis Bleek (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21500. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004164-01; A-side Matrix # B004164-01 LP02-A
        - Memphis Bleek - M.A.D.E. (disc one), 2003; SR-21502; Memphis Bleek (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21503. Double album.
          Catalog # B0000322-01; A-side Matrix # B 0000322-01-LP1-A-RE1
        - Memphis Bleek - M.A.D.E. (disc two), 2003; SR-21503; Memphis Bleek (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21502. Double album.
          Catalog # B0000322-01; A-side Matrix # B 0000322-01-LP02-A-RE1
        - Men At Work - Business as usual, 1982; SR-21504; Men At Work (Box 355)
          Catalog # ARC 37978; A-side Matrix # PAL-37978-IK
        - Men At Work - Dr. Heckyll & Mr. Jive, 1982; SR-21505; Men At Work (Box 355)
          Catalog # AS 1749; A-side Matrix # XSS-169456-1C
        - Men At Work - Who can it be now?; Down under, 1981; SR-21506; Men At Work (Box 355)
          Catalog # AS 1577; A-side Matrix # XSS170731-1A
        - Men Without Hats - I got the message, 1984; SR-21507; Men Without Hats (Box 355)
          Catalog # L33-1164; A-side Matrix # MCA-3780-ASR-1
        - Menace - Marijuana, SR-21508; Menace (Box 355)
          Catalog # AV109; A-side Matrix # AV-109-A
          AV8 Records
        - Menace - Marijuana, SR-21509; Menace (Box 355)
        - Menace - Doghouse, 1989; SR-21510; Menace (Box 355)
          Catalog # JS-1025; A-side Matrix # JS-1025-A
          Jump Street
        - Menace Clan - What you say; Aggravated mayhem, 1995; SR-21511; Menace Clan (Box 355)
          Catalog # SPRO-11079; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11079-A
          Rap-A-Lot Records
        - Menageri - Now I realize, 1993; SR-21512; Menageri (Box 355)
          Catalog # 44 77084; A-side Matrix # XSS-77084-A-1B
        - Menelik & La Tribu - Phénoménélik (disc one), 1995; SR-21513; Menelik & La Tribu (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21514. Double album.
          Catalog # SQT 480765-1; A-side Matrix # 121109-A
          Jimmy Jay Records
        - Menelik & La Tribu - Phénoménélik (disc two), 1995; SR-21514; Menelik & La Tribu (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21513. Double album.
          Catalog # SQT 480765-1; A-side Matrix # 121109-C
        - Mendes, Sergio - Fool on the hill, 1968; SR-21515; Mendes, Sergio; Brazil '66 (Box 355)
          Catalog # SP-4160; A-side Matrix # A+M CSG 4219-1
        - Mental Illness - Nigga noiz; Amazin's not playin', 1994; SR-21516; Mental Illness (Box 356)
          Catalog # 53748-0142-0; A-side Matrix # SS-0142-0 A RE
          StepSun Music Entertainment
        - Menudo - Reaching out, 1984; SR-21517; Menudo (Box 356)
          Catalog # AFL1-4993; A-side Matrix # AL1-4993A-1
        - Menudo - Hold me, 1985; SR-21518; Menudo (Box 356)
          Catalog # JR-14137; A-side Matrix # JR-14137-A-1S
        - Mephisto - Mystery (of love), 1997; SR-21519; Mephisto (Box 356)
          Catalog # SSM 007; A-side Matrix # SSM 007-A
          Sisma Records
        - Mer-Da - Long burn the fire, 1972; SR-21520; Mer-Da (Box 356)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0004; A-side Matrix # DEL-LP-0004
          Funky Delicacies
        - Mercedes - It's your thing, 1999; SR-21521; Mercedes (Box 356)
          Catalog # SPRO 81225; A-side Matrix # 08724-81225-1A
        - Mercedes - Y'all ain't, 1999; SR-21522; Mercedes (Box 356)
          Catalog # SPRO 81263; A-side Matrix # 08724 81263-1-A
        - Mercedes - Callin' (the R Kelly "reggae" flava), 1994; SR-21523; Mercedes; Candee (Box 356)
          Catalog # HOOD-1002; A-side Matrix # HOOD-1002-A
          N' Da Hood Entertainment
        - Mercenaries - Rhymorator; Bounce; Stick up, stick up, 1994; SR-21524; Mercenaries; RMR (Box 356)
          Catalog # MS6502; A-side Matrix # MS-6502-A
          Mercenary Records
        - Mercer, Pat - Thunderbolt | Starvin' for the music, 1978; SR-21525; Mercer, Pat; Doc, Aikens & Shields (Box 356)
          Catalog # V2744; A-side Matrix # V2744-A
          Paradise Records
        - Mercer, Sandy - Work your body (work that body), 1979; SR-21526; Mercer, Sandy (Box 356)
          Catalog # JD-11561; A-side Matrix # PD-11561 A-1
        - Merchant - There must be a way, 1985; SR-21527; Merchant (Box 356)
          Catalog # MCR 375; A-side Matrix # MCR-375-A-RE1
        - Mercury, Eric - Gimme a call sometime, 1981; SR-21528; Mercury, Eric (Box 356)
          Catalog # SPRO-9655; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9655 F-2
        - Mercury, Freddie - I was born to love, 1985; SR-21529; Mercury, Freddie (Box 356)
          Catalog # 44-05197; A-side Matrix # XSS-173298-1A
        - Merge - Take it to the top; Volcanic voodoo, 1982; SR-21530; Merge (Box 356)
          Catalog # JD-13051; A-side Matrix # PD-13051-1-1
        - Merlyn - Spellbound; Incantation, 1999; SR-21531; Merlyn (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21532. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # DS-004; A-side Matrix # DS-004-A
          Dreamscape Recordings
        - M1 - E.F.2000, 1999; SR-21532; M1 (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21531. Different discs.
          Catalog # JX023; A-side Matrix # JX-023-A
          Jinxx Records
          Canada
        - Meshe - Love to love you baby, 1998; SR-21533; Meshe (Box 356)
          Catalog # RPROLP0871; A-side Matrix # 88561-1766-1A
        - Message - Love one another, 1995; SR-21534; Message (Box 356)
          Catalog # CR-344; A-side Matrix # CR-344-A
        - Messiah - Temple of dreams, 1992; SR-21535; Messiah (Box 356)
          Catalog # 0-40655; A-side Matrix # 0-40655
          WHTE LBLS
        - Messinger Service - Get streetwise, 1983; SR-21536; Messinger Service (Box 356)
          Catalog # SSR 114; A-side Matrix # SS-114-A-RE-2
          Silver Screen Records
        - Mestre Suassuna E Dirceu - Capoeira cordão de ouro volume 3, 1983; SR-21537; Mestre Suassuna E Dirceu (Box 356)
          Catalog # 1-04-405-423; A-side Matrix # 1.04-405-423-A1
          Musicolor
          Sao Paulo, Brazil
        - Mestre Suassuna E Dirceu - Capoeira cordão de ouro volume 4, 1978; SR-21538; Mestre Suassuna E Dirceu (Box 356)
          Catalog # 104-405-259; A-side Matrix # 104-405-259-A
        - Meta & Feza - Surprise, SR-21539; Meta & Feza (Box 356)
          Catalog # TAN 7004; A-side Matrix # M6 344205 2
          Tangent
        - Metabass 'n' Breath - Perfection, 1999; SR-21540; Metabass 'n' Breath (Box 356)
          Catalog # MBB04; A-side Matrix # MBB 04A-1B
          MetaBass 'n' Breath
        - Metal Weeds - Sunshine love, 1976; SR-21541; Metal Weeds (Box 356)
          Catalog # KPN1-0179; A-side Matrix # KPN1-0179-A
        - Meters - Let's party with the Meters (disc one), 2001; SR-21542; Meters (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21543. Double album.
          Catalog # GET8006; A-side Matrix # GET 8006 LP 1 A
          Get Back
          Florence, Italy
        - Meters - Let's party with the Meters (disc two), 2001; SR-21543; Meters (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21542. Double album.
          Catalog # GET8006; A-side Matrix # GET 8006 LP 2 A
        - Method Man - Party..., 2001; SR-21544; Method Man; Riley, Teddy (Box 356)
          Catalog # DEFR 15375-1; A-side Matrix # 314-588-694-1A
        - Method Man - Tical 0: the prequel (disc one), 2004; SR-21545; Method Man (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21546. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 548 406-1; A-side Matrix # 314-548-406-1-LP1A
        - Method Man - Tical 0: the prequel (disc two), 2004; SR-21546; Method Man (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21545. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 548 406-1; A-side Matrix # 314-548-406-1-LP2A
        - Method Man - What's happenin', 2004; SR-21547; Method Man (Box 356)
          Catalog # DEFR 16039-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16039-1A
        - Method Man - The show, 2004; SR-21548; Method Man (Box 356)
          Catalog # DEFR 16159-1; A-side Matrix # B0003414-11A
        - Method Man - Tical 0: the prequel (disc one), 2004; SR-21549; Method Man (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21550. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFR 16051-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16051-1-LP1A
        - Method Man - Tical 0: the prequel (disc two), 2004; SR-21550; Method Man (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21549. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFR 16051-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16051-1-LP2A
        - Metro - Here for the love, 1994; SR-21551; Metro (Box 356)
          Catalog # BASSEX 002; A-side Matrix # BASSEX-002-A
          Bassex Records
        - Metro LA - Go with the flow, 1998; SR-21552; Metro LA (Box 356)
          Catalog # BASSEX 016; A-side Matrix # BASSEX-16-A
        - Metro Logic - Snakewalk; Please don't tell me, 1984; SR-21553; Metro Logic (Box 356)
          Catalog # MLMS10001; A-side Matrix # MLMS 10001 A
          Powerplay Records
        - Metro, Peter - Calypso calypso, SR-21554; Metro, Peter; Zuzu (Box 356)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MM007-A
          Witty Music
        - Metro, Peter - Police in a Jamaica, 1985; SR-21555; Metro, Peter (Box 356)
          Catalog # JLT. 004; A-side Matrix # D.S.R. 8054-A-PABLO
          Jah Life Time
        - Metro, Peter - Dibbi dibbi, 1987; SR-21556; Metro, Peter; Sister Charmaine (Box 356)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MM-142-A
        - Mexakinz - Confessions; Hell don't pay, 1995; SR-21557; Mexakinz (Box 356)
          Catalog # 374631372-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 1376-1A SP1
          Mad Sounds Recordings
        - Meyers, Alicia - Alicia, 1980; SR-21558; Meyers, Alicia (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21559. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MCA-5181; A-side Matrix # MCA-2505W2
        - Meyers, Alicia - Alicia, 1980; SR-21559; Meyers, Alicia (Box 356)
          In same jacket as # SR-21558. 2 copies.
        - M.F. Grimm - Get down, 1996; SR-21560; M.F. Grimm (Box 356)
          Catalog # DOL 0224; A-side Matrix # DOL 0224 A
          Dolo Records
        - MFSB - TSOP (the sound of Philadelphia); Love is the message, 1987; SR-21561; MFSB; Three Degrees (Box 356)
          Catalog # 4ZH 06924; A-side Matrix # 4Z8 3711-3-GIA
        - M.I.A. - Mississippi mutants; Schoolcraft bump, 1999; SR-21562; M.I.A. (Box 356)
          Catalog # UR-018; A-side Matrix # UR018-A
          Underground Resistance
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Mendes, Sergio - Greatest hits, 1970; SR-21563; Mendes, Sergio; Brazil '66 (Box 356)
          Catalog # SP 4252; A-side Matrix # A&M CSG-SP4403-4
        - Mensah, E.T. - Highlife giants of Africa - Highlife souvenir volume 1, 1984; SR-21564; Mensah, E.T.; Dr. Victor Olaiya & The International All Stars Band (Box 356)
          Catalog # POLP 102; A-side Matrix # POLP 102
          Nigeria
        - Mental As Anything - Brain brain, 1983; SR-21565; Mental As Anything (Box 356)
          Catalog # SP-17247; A-side Matrix # AM SP 017247-A ES1
        - Mia X - Imma shine, 1999; SR-21566; Mia X (Box 357)
          Catalog # SPRO 81180; A-side Matrix # S-40680
        - Mia X - Watcha wanna do?, 1998; SR-21567; Mia X (Box 357)
          Catalog # SPRO 81121; A-side Matrix # S-39452
        - Mia X - The party don't stop, 1997; SR-21568; Mia X (Box 357)
          Catalog # SPRO 30168; A-side Matrix # S-3828
        - Miami Bass DJ's - The birthday jam (it's your birthday), 1994; SR-21569; Miami Bass DJ's (Box 357)
          Catalog # VR-1293; A-side Matrix # VR-1293-A
        - Miami Boyz - Do you want to party, 1988; SR-21570; Miami Boyz (Box 357)
          Catalog # OT 8001; A-side Matrix # ON TOP-8001-A
          On Top Records
        - Miami Sound Machine - I want you to love me, 1978; SR-21571; Miami Sound Machine (Box 357)
          Catalog # EC-1703; A-side Matrix # EC-1703-A
          Electric Cat
        - Miami Sound Machine - Conga!, 1985; SR-21572; Miami Sound Machine (Box 357)
          Catalog # 49-05253; A-side Matrix # XSS-174519-1A
        - Miami Vice - Tribute to K.C. & The Sunshine Band, 1987; SR-21573; Miami Vice (Box 357)
          Catalog # AD 127832; A-side Matrix # AD 127832-A1
          Adventure Dance
          Belgium
        - Miami Vice - The winning streak, 1985; SR-21574; Miami Vice (Box 357)
          Catalog # TEN 67-12; A-side Matrix # TEN 6712 A-2U-1-1
          10 Records
        - Miami Vice - The winning streak, 1985; SR-21575; Miami Vice (Box 357)
        - Mic Geronimo - Masta I.C. (remix); Shit's real (remix), 1994; SR-21576; Mic Geronimo (Box 357)
          Catalog # TVT4911-0; A-side Matrix # TVT4911-0A
          Blunt Recordings
        - Mic Geronimo - Nothin' but the money; Usual suspects, 1997; SR-21577; Mic Geronimo (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21578. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TVT-4931-OP; A-side Matrix # TVT-4931-OP-A
        - Mic Geronimo - Nothin' but the money; Usual suspects, 1997; SR-21578; Mic Geronimo (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21577. 2 copies.
        - Mic Little - Put it in a letter; Golden state, 2006; SR-21579; Mic Little; Ne-Yo (Box 357)
          Catalog # DEFR 16614-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16614-1A
        - Mic-T - The recipe (remix); What's a M.C.; Doin it right, 2000; SR-21580; Mic-T (Box 357)
          Catalog # HTKO17; A-side Matrix # HTK-017-A RE1
          Heratik Productions
          Oakland, California
        - Mic-T - Michael Wallstreet (sadomasochist) (disc one), 2000; SR-21581; Mic-T (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21582. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK009; A-side Matrix # HTK009 A
        - Mic-T - Michael Wallstreet (sadomasochist) (disc two), 2000; SR-21582; Mic-T (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21581. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK009; A-side Matrix # HTK009 C
        - Mag 7 - Sumthin' terrible, 1999; SR-21583; Mag 7 (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21584. 2 copies.
          Catalog # U8P-1488; A-side Matrix # U8P-1488-A
          Biv 10 Records
        - Mag 7 - Sumthin' terrible, 1999; SR-21584; Mag 7 (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21583. 2 copies.
        - Michael, George - Faith, 1987; SR-21585; Michael, George (Box 357)
          Catalog # 44 07478; A-side Matrix # XSS176387-1A
        - Michael, George - Father figure, 1987; SR-21586; Michael, George (Box 357)
          Catalog # 44 07547; A-side Matrix # XSS177507-1A
        - Michael, George - Hard day (special remix), 1987; SR-21587; Michael, George (Box 357)
          Catalog # 44 07466; A-side Matrix # XSS176061-1A
        - Michael, George - Monkey, 1987; SR-21588; Michael, George (Box 357)
          Catalog # 44 07849; A-side Matrix # XSS-07849A-1A
        - Michael, George - Spinning the wheel, 1996; SR-21589; Michael, George (Box 357)
          Catalog # PRO-A-5001; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-5001-PRM-A
          DreamWorks SKG Records
        - Michaels, Christian - I am, 2000; SR-21590; Michaels, Christian (Box 357)
          Catalog # FW001; A-side Matrix # FW-001 A
          Funk Wax
          Orlando, Florida
        - Michaels, Jordan - Wild thing; Phases, 1965; SR-21591; Michaels, Jordan (Box 357)
          Catalog # HT-008; A-side Matrix # HT008
          Erika Records
        - Michaels, Lee - Live (disc one), 1973; SR-21592; Michaels, Lee (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21593. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-3518; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 3551-P1
        - Michaels, Lee - Live (disc two), 1973; SR-21593; Michaels, Lee (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21592. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-3518; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 3553-P1
        - Michaels, Lee - 5th, 1971; SR-21594; Michaels, Lee (Box 357)
          Catalog # SP-4302; A-side Matrix # SP-4503
        - Michele - Disco dance, 1977; SR-21595; Michele (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21596. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WES 12110; A-side Matrix # WES 12110A70314
        - Michele - Disco dance, 1977; SR-21596; Michele (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21595. 2 copies.
        - Michele, Yvette - Everyday & everynight (remix), 1996; SR-21597; Michele, Yvette (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21598. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RDAB-64509-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64509-1-A1
          Loud Records
        - Michele, Yvette - Everyday & everynight (remix), 1996; SR-21598; Michele, Yvette (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21597. 2 copies.
        - Michele, Yvette - DJ keep playin' (get your music on), 1997; SR-21599; Michele, Yvette (Box 357)
          Catalog # RDAB-64981-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB- 64981-1-A
        - Michele, Yvette - Everyday & everynight, 1995; SR-21600; Michele, Yvette (Box 357)
          Catalog # RDAB 66450-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64450-1-A1
        - Michel'le - Hang tyme, 1998; SR-21601; Michel'le (Box 357)
          Catalog # SPRO 30248; A-side Matrix # SPRO 30248-A
          Death Row Records
        - Michie Mee and L.A. Luv - Victory is calling; On this mic, 1988; SR-21602; Michie Mee and L.A. Luv (Box 357)
          Catalog # 0-96593; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56294-56295-3
          First Priority Music
        - Michigan & Smiley - Tom's diner, 1991; SR-21603; Michigan & Smiley (Box 357)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # R1PH6A
          Penthouse Records
          Queens, New York
        - Michigan & Smiley - Sugar daddy; What a life, 1983; SR-21604; Michigan & Smiley (Box 357)
          Catalog # RAS 7003; A-side Matrix # RAS7003A
        - Michigan & Smiley - Come when Jah call you; Ghetto man, 1982; SR-21605; Michigan & Smiley (Box 357)
          Catalog # VPRD 90; A-side Matrix # VPRD 90-A
          Jah Guidance
        - Michigan & Smiley - Diseases | Boneman connection, 2000; SR-21606; Michigan & Smiley; Nicodemus (Box 357)
          Catalog # VPRD-6342; A-side Matrix # VPRD-6342-A
        - Michigan & Smiley - Diseases (hip hop), 1992; SR-21607; Michigan & Smiley (Box 357)
          Catalog # MR 04; A-side Matrix # MR 004-A
          Michigan Records
        - Monday Michiru - Sunshine after the rain, 2000; SR-21608; Monday Michiru (Box 357)
          Catalog # MAW-055; A-side Matrix # MAW-055-A
        - George Mickens & The Crew - Rock & Freak, 1987; SR-21609; George Mickens & The Crew (Box 357)
          Catalog # NR 17193-1; A-side Matrix # NR-171931
          Mickens
        - Mickey - Give me a break, SR-21610; Mickey (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21611. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CBR-MS/022; A-side Matrix # 0207X33-A
          Baltimore Breakbeats Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Mickey - Give me a break, SR-21611; Mickey (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21610. 2 copies.
        - Mickey & The Soul Generation - Iron Leg: The Complete Mickey & The Soul Generation, 2002; SR-21612; Mickey & The Soul Generation (Box 357)
          Catalog # CT-102; A-side Matrix # CT 102
          Cali-Tex Records
          Mill Valley, California
        - Micky Slick - Hardcore, 1984; SR-21613; Micky Slick (Box 357)
          Catalog # PLS M501; A-side Matrix # HARDCORE-A
          Pleasure Records
          Stockholm, Sweden
        - Micro Wave - Star search, 1987; SR-21614; Micro Wave (Box 357)
          Catalog # 44 07841; A-side Matrix # XSS 07841 A 1A
        - Micranots - Pitch black ark; Exodus, 2000; SR-21615; Micranots (Box 357)
          Catalog # BDS-846; A-side Matrix # BDS-846-A
          Subversive Music
        - Micro - Sound barrier, 2000; SR-21616; Micro (Box 357)
          Catalog # MM 88468-1; A-side Matrix # MM88468-1A
          West Hollywood, California
        - Micro - Electric; Impact (the mixes), 1996; SR-21617; Micro; Vicious Vic (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21618. Different discs.
          Catalog # CF 2833; A-side Matrix # CF2833A
          Massapequa, New York
        - Hoodwink - X travagant, SR-21618; Hoodwink (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21617. Different discs.
          Catalog # 2# Gazoo; A-side Matrix # HDO11
        - MCL (Micro Chip League) - New York; Communicate, 1988; SR-21619; MCL (Micro Chip League) (Box 357)
          Catalog # OLR 129; A-side Matrix # OLR-129-A
          Oak Lawn Records
          Dallas, Texas
        - Micronawts - Smurph across the surf, 1982; SR-21620; Micronawts (Box 357)
          Catalog # TC-0002; A-side Matrix # TC-0002-A
        - Micronawts - (I can do it...You can do it) letzmurph acrossdasurf, 1982; SR-21621; Micronawts (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21622. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TC-0002; A-side Matrix # TC0002A
        - Micronawts - (I can do it...You can do it) letzmurph acrossdasurf, 1982; SR-21622; Micronawts (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21621. 2 copies.
        - Micronawts - Smurph across the surf, 1982; SR-21623; Micronawts (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21624. 2 copies.
        - Micronawts - Smurph across the surf, 1982; SR-21624; Micronawts (Box 357)
          In same jacket as # SR-21623. 2 copies.
        - Middleton, Tom - A Jedi's night out (Disc one), 1999; SR-22151; Middleton, Tom (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22152; SR-22153. Triple album.
          Catalog # MMLLP027; A-side Matrix # MLV-005-A
          Mixmag Live!
          Slough, United Kingdom
        - Middleton, Tom - A Jedi's night out (Disc two), 1999; SR-22152; Middleton, Tom (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22151; SR-22153. Triple album.
          Catalog # MMLLP027; A-side Matrix # MLV-005-C